Pokemon Battle Sim [Alpha] README.txt

Instructions

If you know how to play Pokemon or Pokemon Showdown, this is pretty self-explainatory. 
Except this is a really crappy version of it with terrible graphics, only 2 moves per pokemon,
broken game mechanics, and no switching. 
Controls use the mouse (Except for text input)
Moves can be used by clicking on the name of the move.

Anyways I hope you enjoy my game.

Shoutout to Jasper Meggit for teaching me basic graphics and ui.

[=============================================================================================]

All images are © The Pokémon Company International
I totally did not steal sprites from online ;)

[=============================================================================================]

MIT License

Copyright (c) 2017 Andy Shi

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.

[=============================================================================================]
